

# STEFANA SAVOVA

Junior .NET Developer ♥ SOFIA, 1700, BULGARIA +359 883 483 730

#### O DETAILS O

2-B Visarion Belinski street, 3rd floor, apartment 25, Sofia, 1700, Bulgaria +359 883 483 730 stefana.t.savova@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

14/12/1992 Bulgaria

NATIONALITY

Bulgarian

o LINKS o

<u>GitHub</u>

LinkedIn

O LANGUAGES O

English

### PROFILE

In my short professional experience, I've worked as an employee and as a manager. I believe that this has highly raised my sense of responsibility towards the working process. I know how to follow the instructions of a leader and I am perfectly capable of making decisions, concerning my personal professional duties. I believe that in the balance between those two abilities lies the key to an efficient working process.

As a manager in a micro company, providing direct services, communication was utterly important for fulfilling my duties. I believe I possess the necessary communication skills as well as the ability to adapt to new and dynamic environments. I am confident that I fit perfectly in every team and working with me would bring synergy to the outcome.

I do not have any technical professional experience in the Software industry yet, but my educational adventure in SoftUni makes me confident that I am a fast learner and I am able to adapt quickly to the dynamic and challenging environment of Information technology. Moreover I have already been part of an R&D team in Maj.io, but in a different role. Which makes me organizationally prepared to step in quickly in the team work.

Driven by my strong motivation and persistency I believe that in short terms I can dive into the nature of the work and become a vital and useful part of every team.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Manager at Regal Services ltd., Sofia

November 2018 — February 2019

Base Manager at Regal Services ltd., Sofia

November 2017 - November 2018

HR Associate at Maj.io, Sofia

October 2014 — April 2015

Manually training software algorythm for parsing employees data and matching it to an appropriate employer.

# EDUCATION

ASP.NET Core, Software University, Sofia

C# Web Basics, Software University, Sofia

Databases Advanced - Entity Framework, Software University, Sofia

Databases basics - MS SQL Server, Software University, Sofia

